So, what is this?
이게 뭐라고?
Googlie Worm.
퉁방울눈지렁이
And this?
그럼 이건?
Glow Pop Jiggly Jam.
빛나리폭탄꿈틀이죽
It's so funny!
진짜 웃긴다
그럼 이건 뭐야?
What's this?
A hunk of sandwich from last year.
작년에 먹던 샌드위치 조각
뭐가 걸렸다!
아주 큰 놈인데?
Geller's got one hooked!
Looks like a big one!
인간과 자연의 사투가...
It's the classic struggle
between man
Someone knocked over a lamp.
누가 램프를 넘어뜨렸네
You know what'll be great
about the fishing trip?
올해 낚시여행의
하이라이트는 이거야
When my Dad asks, "What are you
doing with your life?"...
아버지가 호수에서 묻겠지
'너 계속 그렇게 살 거냐?'
...I can say, "I'm doing a movie
with Charlton Heston.
'전 찰턴 헤스턴하고 영화 찍는데
아버진 계속 그렇게 사실래요?'
What about you?"
Don't stop having fun
just because I'm here.
나 신경 쓰지 말고 재미들 봐
캐시가 너희를 다 배신했냐?
Kathy didn't cheat on all of you.
Well, except you.
너는 빼고
You know what is so sweet? Those birds
have not left his side the whole time.
참 기특하지?
주인 옆을 떠나지 않아
Yeah, I wish that rooster were dead.
수탉은 죽었으면 좋겠다
You shouldn't leave Chandler alone.
They broke up only two days ago.
조이, 챈들러 혼자 두지 마
겨우 이틀 전에 실연 당했어
Go fishing next week.
낚시는 다음주에 가라
There's nothing I can do.
He's still in his sweats.
지금은 나도 별 도움이 안돼
땀복 착용은 1단계란 뜻이야
That's only phase one.
2단계 때 돌아올게
그걸 놓칠 순 없지
I'll be back for phase two.
I'd never miss that.
Phase two?
2단계가 뭔데?
Getting drunk
and going to a strip club.
고주망태가 돼서
스트립클럽에 가지
How does going there
make him better?
스트립클럽이 무슨 도움이 돼?
There are naked ladies there.
홀딱 벗은 여자들이 있어
Then to phase three:
seeing yourself with other women.
다음은 다른 여자와 뒹구는
자신을 상상하는 3단계지
There are naked ladies there too.
- 역시 벗은 여자들이 나와
- 그럼
1분만 혼자 있게 해줘!
Would you give me one minute, please?
The One with Joey's Dirty Day
These will match the jacket
you picked out last week?
지난주에 골라준
재킷과 어울릴까요?
네
There we go.
그렇죠
There it is.
아주 좋아요
You know what I need?
Gloves.
참, 장갑도 필요하군요
정장용 갈색 가죽장갑
Brown leather dress gloves.
알았어요, 좀 볼까요?
이쪽 손은 꽤 크군요
Well, let's see....
This one is large.
And this one....
- 그리고 이쪽 손은...
- 역시 크죠?
Also large?
네, 그래요
큰 거 두 장 준비하죠
Two larges coming right up.
Hello.
-Damn you.
-Could I have a moment?
망할 것!
- 레이첼, 나 좀 볼까요?
- 네
My niece, you see,
is in town from London.
런던에서 조카딸이 왔는데
정확히 말하면 슈롭셔지만
Shropshire, but you know.
She's about your age, I'd say.
레이첼 또래예요
아무튼 오페라 티켓이
있어요, '박쥐'라고...
Anyway, I have tickets for the opera.
Die Fledermaus.
Would you like to keep her
company tonight?
오늘 저녁 함께
가줬으면 하는데
네, 그러죠, 믿으세요
갈게요, 박쥐? 좋죠
Sure. You got it!
Count me in. Me.
Fledermaus. Great!
그럴게요
오! 그래요, 고마워요
감사해요, 정말 고마워요
Yes, of course.
Thank you so very much.
So?
자...
그럼...
장갑?
-Gloves?
-Sorry, I'll be right back.
오! 그렇죠
잠시만요
Actually, I got to take off.
난 지금 가봐야 되는데
혹시 저녁에 계획 있어요?
I was curious.
Do you have plans tonight?
No, nothing!
아뇨, 전혀!
내가 투자한 나이트클럽이
오늘 문 여는데 와볼래요?
I invested in a nightclub.
It opens tonight. Want to come?
That would be great!
네, 좋죠
You're into hard-core S & M, right?
하드코어 변태 취향이군요
-Well, I guess.
-I'm kidding.
- 저기 그건...
- 농담입니다
일찍 가서 VIP명단에
올려놓죠, 날 찾아요
I'll put you on the VlP list.
Look for me.
네, 꼭 갈게요
Great! You bet.
- 이따 봅시다
- 알았어요
I'll see you tonight.
그럼
- 티켓을 잊을 뻔했군요
- 네?
-I almost forgot the tickets.
-What?
For you and Emily. Tonight.
Die Fledermaus.
당신과 에밀리
오늘밤, 박쥐...
어... 그렇군요
Oh, right.
3대 테너 중 두 명이
나오니까 볼만할 거요
You'll like it.
It has two out of the three tenors.
오, 저런!
I can't believe
Kathy did this to me.
캐시가 이럴 수 있어?
내 짝이라고 믿었는데
I really thought she was the one.
I'll tell you what.
잘 들어, 이 의자에서
꼼짝도 안 할 거야
I'm not getting out
of this chair. Ever!
지금부터 얘가 내 짝이야
From now on, this chair is the one!
You know what else is the one?
My sweatpants.
이 땀복도 내 짝이고
제발 그 땀복이나 벗어라
그거 벗고 한번 놀아보자
Just take the sweats off, okay?
Take them off
and we'll have some fun.
Wow, and I can't resist that line.
That's why I never wear sweatpants.
난 그런 유혹 못 참아
그래서 땀복을 안 입지
- 얘들아
- 왔구나
- 뭐 좀 잡았어?
- 너흰 상상도 못할 거야
Did you catch any fish?
You guys have no idea.
- 냄새야!
- 너무 독하다
-You stink!
-Are you kidding?
Three days without a shower.
Plus, I fell in a big tub of worms!
사흘 동안 샤워도 못한 데다
낚시가게 지렁이 통에 빠졌어
How's he doing?
저 녀석은 어때?
이틀째 저 의자에 붙어있어
He hasn't left
that chair in two days.
임마, 잘 살았냐?
Hey, buddy, how's it going?
봐, 친구가 오니까
살아나잖아
You see? He just needed
his pal to come home.
I got to memorize my lines.
대사나 외우련다
내일 찰턴 헤스턴과의
극적인 만남을 위하여!
Me and Charlton Heston,
bright and early tomorrow, baby!
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
모니카
What's the matter?
무슨 일 있구나?
Joshua invited me to this
fancy club opening tonight.
조슈아가 오늘밤 클럽
오픈에 날 초대했는데
But I already told Mr. Waltham...
난 월섬 씨 조카딸 데리고
따분한 오페라에 가야 돼
...that I would take his niece
to the dumb old opera.
So, what are you going to do?
어떡하냐?
- 난 모르겠다
- 안돼! 도와줘!
-I don't know.
-No! Help me!
난 일 나가야 돼
-I can't. I have to work.
-Phoebe?
피비?
I would, but I get
my morning sickness in the evening.
도와주고 싶지만
난 밤에 입덧이 심해져
아니다, 밤새 내 뒤통수
붙잡아줄 수 있대?
Unless she wants to spend the night
holding my hair back for me.
You guys, come on!
I have to meet Joshua.
제발 이러지 마
난 꼭 만나야 돼
It's my one chance for him
to see the "fun" Rachel.
'재미있는 레이첼'을
보여줄 기회라고
The "wouldn't it be great
if she were my wife?" Rachel.
'아내로 삼고 싶은
레이첼' 말이야
조이랑 챈들러 있어?
Are Joey and Chandler back?
챈들러는 아직도 1단계고
조이는 이 냄새의 주인공이야
Chandler's still in phase one,
and Joey's that thing you smell.
안녕?
So....
혹시...
No.
- 싫어요
- 오, 제발...
Come on!
-She's here.
-Wait, wait.
- 왔나보다
- 잠깐만, 로스
Ross, please?
부탁이야
생전 처음 보는 여자랑
오페라를 보러 가라?
You want me to take some girl
I've never met to the opera...
넌 클럽에서 딴 남자랑
새롱거리게? 흠...
...so you can go to a club
and flirt with some guy?
That is a toughie.
너무 힘든 사안이군
She's looking down the hall.
복도를 둘러보는데?
She looked right at me.
날 쳐다봤어
You can't see people
through that hole, can you?
참, 이쪽은 안 보이지?
안녕하세요?
계세요?
금방 나갈게요! 부탁이야
이미 다 지난 일이잖아
I'll be right there!
Okay, Ross, please.
I thought we had moved on.
I thought we could be happy
for each other.
서로의 행복을 빌어주자
나 혼자만 그런 거야?
I mean, was that just me?
All right, I'll do it.
- 알았어
- 고마워, 무지하게 고마워
Thank you, thank you.
Emily.
I'm Rachel Greene.
- 에밀리?
- 네
레이첼 그린이에요
제대로 찾았군요
Thank goodness!
There's been a teeny change of plans.
I'm not free tonight
계획에 사소한 변동이
생겼어요, 제가 바빠서...
그래요?
Really?
I must've missed your call, though
I didn't leave the flat all day.
멋지군요, 종일 집에 있으면서
댁의 전화를 못 받았다니
- 사실은...
- 아뇨, 괜찮아요
Well, l
That's not rude.
It's in keeping with the trip...
어차피 당신들 소시지 마차에
치어죽을 뻔한 여행이니까
...where I've been run down
by one of your wiener carts...
또 존 F. 케네디
공항의 알몸수색
...and been strip-searched
at the airport.
Apparently, I look like someone who's
got cocaine stuffed up their bum.
내가 아랫도리에 코카인이나
끼워 올 인간처럼 보였겠죠?
I think you look great.
제가 볼 땐 멀쩡하네요
Good night.
It was very nice to meet you.
잘 있어요
정말 반가웠어요
I'll get her.
잡아올게
Please, hurry.
- 빨리 가
- 알았어
억양이 진짜 귀엽지?
Don't you just love
the way they talk?
-What?
-The baby kicked!
왜?
- 발길질을 했어
- 세상에
Oh, my God.
No, wait. The elastic
in my underwear busted.
아니, 속옷고무줄
끊어진 거다
아뿔싸! 늦잠 잤다!
Oh, my God! I overslept!
I was supposed to be
on the set half an hour ago!
30분 전에 촬영장에
가있어야 하는데
그 냄새를 풍기면서 갈 거야?
You can't go like that!
You stink!
I fell asleep.
Now I don't have time!
지금 샤워할 시간이 없어
Just 10 blocks away.
If I run, I'll make it.
열 블록 밖이니까
뛰어가면 될 거야
열 블록 뛰고 나면
냄새 더 죽이겠다
Run 10 blocks.
That'll help the smell.
천천히 가
아니, 빨랑 사라져
Slow down!
No, keep moving.
어제 조슈아랑 어땠어?
How did it go last night?
조슈아는 코빼기도 못 보고
어떤 여자한테 주먹을 날렸어
Well, I didn't see Joshua.
But I did punch a girl in the face.
- 뭐?
- 왜?
The whole night was horrible.
It was pouring.
비까지 퍼붓고 끔찍한 밤이었어
There was no Rachel Greene on the list.
But there was a Rachel Greep.
거기 갔더니 명단에
레이첼 그린은 없고
레이첼 그립만 있더라
So did you get to meet her?
그래서 그 여자 만났어?
There is no Rachel Greep.
But this girl overheard us.
레이첼 그립이란
여자는 없는데
어떤 여자가 그 말을 듣고
자기가 레이첼 그립이래
And she said, "I'm Rachel Greep!"
And he let her in.
결국 그 여자가 들어갔어
So you hit her?
그 여자를 쳤니?
아니, 뒤에 서있던 뚱보년이
내 우산을 훔치려고 하잖아
No, she was already in.
This big bitch behind me
tried to steal my umbrella...
면상을 봐줬지
...so I clocked her.
미치겠다, 작은 바람이라면
밖에서 조슈아를 잠깐 만나
All I wanted was a few hours...
...outside of work to see Joshua...
...so he could go ahead and
start falling in love with me.
내 포로로 만드는 게 다야
오, 피브스...
Pheebs.
Honey, that's your name.
그건 네 이름이잖아
That's short for Phoebe? I thought
that's what we called each other.
그게 피비의 애칭이었어?
우리끼리 부르는 이름인 줄 알았네
-You're wearing pants!
-That's right.
바지 갈아입었네?
그래, 사내놈들 다 어디 갔어
술과 스트립쇼가 기다리는데
Where are the guys? I'm ready
to get drunk and see strippers.
아침 9시 반이야
It's 9:30 a.m.
They got a breakfast buffet.
아침 뷔페도 있어
여보세요, 오빠?
바꿔줘
Let me talk to him!
-Oh, my God!
-Can't I just?
세상에!
- 이리 줘봐...
- 쉬잇! 뭐라고?
- 대체 이 집 주인이 누구야
- 쉿! 시끄러워! 뭐래?
-It's my phone and she's shush
-Please!
What's he saying?
He's with Emily in Vermont.
버몬트의 민박집에
에밀리랑 같이 있대
What? Oh, my God!
뭐? 웬일이니!
에밀리가 누구야?
아니 되오!
Who the hell is Emily?
No.
When we first met her,
she was soaking, her feet were wet....
처음 봤을 땐 발끝까지
젖어서 꼴이 엉망이었는데
Who wouldn't be miserable?
I'm telling you, once l
got her into a dry pair of shoes...
마른 구두로 갈아 신으니까
완전히 딴 사람이야
...she was a totally different person.
They're in Vermont?
How did this happen?
버몬트에 있어?
이래도 돼?
아야!
How'd he end up in Vermont
with that witch?
어떻게 그 여우랑
버몬트까지 가!
Maybe she doesn't hit him
all the time.
그 여우는 너처럼
사람을 안 패겠지
There's a deer outside
eating fruit from the orchard!
나와 봐요, 과수원에서 사슴이
과일을 먹고 있어요
I got to go! There's a deer
eating fruit from the orchard!
끊는다, 과수원에서 사슴이
과일을 먹고 있대!
He had to go. There was a deer
eating fruit from the orchard.
끊었어, 과수원에서 사슴이
과일을 먹고 있대
I don't get this.
She was horrible!
뭐야, 그 여자
형편없었잖아!
난 저리 간다
I'm going to go stand over there.
Why do you care?
왜 그렇게 신경을 써?
I don't care.
신경 안 써
조슈아랑 꼬여서 그런 거지만
I'm just upset that
I'm getting nowhere with Joshua.
처음 만난 여자랑
낼름 버몬트로 날아가?
You do not just meet someone
and go flitting off to Vermont!
너도 배리랑 만나자마자
베일로 날아갔었잖아
When you first met Barry,
you flitted off to Vail.
그렇게 시시콜콜한 건
한 번쯤 잊어주면 안돼?
Could you, just for once...
...not remember every little thing?
So you know, when's he getting back?
그래서 언제쯤 돌아온대?
A couple of days.
며칠 후에
I knew something
like this would happen.
내 이렇게 될 줄 알았지
What are you doing?
무슨 짓이야
챈들러, 단계를
되돌릴 순 없어
You can't go back a phase!
You're thinking about time.
You can't go back in time.
있어, 되돌릴 수 없는 건
시간이야
그러지 말고 2단계
스트립클럽 우리랑 가자
Why don't you do your phase two
strip club thing with us?
그래, 우리가 남자친구 해줄게
We can be guys!
그건 불가능해
No, you can't.
Let us be guys!
Maybe we want to be guys.
남자 할게
남자 되고 싶어
No, you don't. You'd be all
hairy and wouldn't live as long.
남자 되면 털 나고
평균수명도 짧아져
Would you just stop being
such a wuss and get those off?
바보짓 집어치우고
당장 그거 벗어!
And come with us
and watch naked girls dance!
잔말 말고 스트립쇼 보러 가!
Okay.
알았어
I'm sorry.
미안해
실버컵 스튜디오
Joey Tribbiani.
I'm here.
조이 트리비아니 지금 왔습니다
Calm down, we got time.
We're running late.
시간 있으니까 진정해요
촬영이 늦어지는군요
All set.
준비됐네
Look at that.
Charlton Heston eating licorice.
봐요, 찰턴 헤스턴이
감초사탕을 먹다니
Yeah, he loves them.
I've never seen him with
꽤 좋아하시죠
틈만 나면...
와우, 저런!
이게 뭐죠?
What the hell is that?
What smells so bad?
냄새 고약하군
You.
당신 냄새요
I could see why you would think that.
But you know who it is?
그렇게 보일 수도 있지만...
진짜 누군지 알아요?
You?
당신?
No, no. It's Heston.
아뇨... 헤스턴이에요
What?
뭐요?
정말 심하네
He reeks like he went on a three-day
fishing trip, then ate licorice.
사흘 동안 낚시 다녀와서
감초사탕 먹는 모습이야
No way. He's the only one
with a shower in his dressing room.
그럴 리가 없소, 분장실에
전용 샤워시설까지 있는데
Really? A shower?
그래요? 샤워시설?
그 방이 어디죠?
Which room might that be?
The one with "Heston" on it.
'헤스턴'이라고 적힌 데요
그거 흥미롭구만
Interesting.
토플리스 바
고고 걸스
얘, 잔돈으로 바꿔왔어
저 여자 팬티에 꽂을래?
I got some ones.
You want to put them in her panties?
No, thanks, Mom!
됐어요, 엄마!
어머, 그거 안돼요
That.
꺼주세요
임신 중이라
You have to put that out
because I'm pregnant.
Maybe you and your baby
ought to go to another strip club.
그럼 댁의 아기 데리고
다른 클럽에 가보셔
내 아이 아니지롱, 허허
It's not my baby.
Very good.
잘했어요, 멋져요
좋은 구경했네요
진짜 끝내준다
Really good. I enjoyed it.
Very exotic.
I just checked our messages
and Joshua didn't call.
응답기 확인해봤는데
조슈아 전화는 없었어
You'd think he'd be worried
about me not showing up.
내가 안 나타났는데
걱정도 안 되나?
You know what makes it worse?
설상가상이다
Ross is all happy in Vermont.
로스는 버몬트에서
깨가 쏟아지는데
Come on, look where you are!
여긴 더 좋잖아!
Another round of daiquiris.
여기요, 다이커리
한 잔씩 더 주세요
Virgin for me.
알죠? 난 버진으로
Don't let me leave without
the name of that carpet guy.
아까 그 안내원 남자
이름 꼭 알아다줘요
이것 좀 올려요
Come on!
못살아!
You know what?
I'll go home and call Kathy.
집에 가서 캐시한테
전화나 해야겠다
If it'll help.
- 좋도록 해
- 안돼, 그건 테스트였어
That was a test.
In a few hours, I'll be drunk.
이따 내가 취해서 캐시한테
전화하려면 너희가 말려야지
I'll want to call her.
You'll have to stop me.
Then I'll be so drunk,
I'll want to call Janice.
완전히 꼭지가 돌면
재니스한테 전화할 걸?
- 해봐, 어떻게 지낸대?
- 오!
You should! How is she?
I think somebody needs
another lap dance.
또 랩댄스 들어온다
실례해요, 누구시죠?
Who's in there?
How you doing?
안녕하세요?
Who in the hell are you?
자넨 뭔가
Would you believe me
if I said I was Kirk Douglas?
커크 더글라스라면
안 믿으시겠죠?
Put some pants on, kid,
so I can kick your butt.
엉덩이를 질러줄 테니
어서 옷이나 걸치게
아뇨, 잘 모르시나 본데
전 배우입니다
No, wait. You don't understand.
I'm an actor.
Joey Tribbiani.
I'm doing a scene with you today.
조이 트리비아니입니다
오늘 촬영이 있는데
꼴이 엉망이라서
And I stink!
You're in this picture?
이 영화에 출연한다고?
네, 선생님이 포악하다고 함께
근무하길 꺼리는 경찰 역이죠
I'm a cop who won't work with you
because you're a loose cannon.
Anyway, I'm really sorry.
실례인 줄 압니다만
제 꼴이 너무 엉망이라
But I stink.
Joey, right?
- 조이라고 했나?
- 네
Every actor, one time or another
배우라면 누구나
한 번쯤, 기상!
Every actor thinks he stinks.
자기가 엉망이라고 생각하지
Even Laurence Olivier
sometimes thought he stank.
로렌스 올리비에도 가끔은
자신이 엉망인 줄 알았고
Bob Redford won't even watch himself.
로버트 레드포드는
자기 연기를 혐오했지
그런 게 아니라...
You don't understand.
Listen to me.
- 끝까지 들어
- 네에...
I don't know one actor
worth his salt...
제대로 된 배우라면 그런 말
한 번쯤 안 해본 사람은 없네
...who, one time in his career,
didn't say, "God, I stink!"
I just did a scene out there.
First take, I stunk the place up.
방금 찍었던 첫 번째 테이크
나도 죽을 쑤고 말았지
하지만 이걸 반드시 명심하게
The important thing,
and you must remember...
...no matter how badly
you think you stink...
아무리 자신이 엉망이더라도
...you must never, ever bust into
my dressing room and use my shower!
절대로 내 분장실에 침입해
샤워기를 쓰면 안돼!
Do you understand me?
내 말 알아들었나?
-Yes, sir. I'm very sorry.
-Wait a minute!
- 네, 대단히 송구합니다
- 대기! 옷 가져가
Take your pants.
그렇군요
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
정말 죄송합니다
What a business.
재미난 바닥이야
We did okay
at the strip club, right?
우리 클럽에서 잘했지?
Great. Thanks to you,
the hottest waitress is quitting...
그래, 좋았어
덕분에 그 칵테일 아가씨는
초등학교 교사로 나간단다!
...to teach the third grade!
-He still hasn't called.
-Who, Josh?
기가 막혀
아직도 전화 안 했어
누구, 조쉬?
It's Joshua.
조슈아야
-He doesn't like "Josh"?
-No, I don't.
- 조쉬는 싫대?
- 내가 싫어
I'm going to put my sweats back on.
난 다시 땀복 입을래
안돼! 잠깐, 네 말이 맞는데
왜 남자 역할 못한 줄 알아?
You know what?
You were right.
We weren't great at being guys.
You know why?
Because we're girls.
우린 여자니까
그래?
-You know what girls are good at?
-Stripping!
- 여자들 진짜 특기가 뭐게?
- 옷 벗는 거!
No, listening!
얘길 들어주는 거야! 앉아
Sit.
Maybe it would really, really help
if you would just talk.
그냥 얘기만 해도
기분이 나아질 거야
Yeah, come on.
What's going on in there?
그래, 이 속을 시원하게 까발려
혹시 울고 싶어?
그것도 괜찮아
And you know, if you want to cry,
that's okay too.
I'm going to have
to ask you all to leave.
자, 그만들 가줄래?
챈들러
됐어, 노력했지만
3단계는 불가능해
Forget it. We tried,
but phase three is a lost cause.
그 여자들이 아무리 화끈해도
함께 있는 모습이 안 그려져
Those strippers were hot, and l
couldn't picture myself with them.
They really were pretty,
weren't they?
진짜 예쁘긴 하더라
- 전투기 조종사는 최고였어
- 캔디? 숨이 컥 막히더라
-I liked that fighter pilot one.
-Candy?
She was so spunky!
그래
I think if I were going
to be with a woman...
내가 여자를 고른다면...
...it'd be with someone
like Michelle.
미셸 같은 애가 좋아
조그만 게 그냥!
She was just so petite.
For me, it would have to be Chantal.
난 샨탈이 맘에 들던데
- 헉! 샨탈...
- 이건 세상에...
She had the smoothest skin.
피부가 얼마나 매끄럽던지
끈에다 돈을 끼워주면서
I stuck that dollar in
her G-string and grazed her thigh
- 허벅지를 스쳤는데...
- 3단계!
Phase three!
I just achieved phase three!
나 드디어 3단계야!
진짜?
I am totally picturing you
with all those women!
너희가 그 여자들과
뒹구는 모습이 선해!
That's not phase three.
- 그건 3단계가 아냐
- 거기 나도 있거든!
Well, I'm there too!
Are we all together in a group?
- 그럼 우리 모두 함께?
- 스톱! 코피 터진다!
Stop it, you're killing me!
I think I moved on to phase four!
이건 아무래도 4단계야!
-What is that?
-I don't want a relationship ever!
그건 뭔데?
우정이고 나발이고
치마 두른 애들 다 덤벼!
I just want sex
with strippers and my friends!
Come on.
어서, 웃는 얼굴 좀 보자
Let me see that smile.
I don't want to.
싫어
Please?
착하지?
I wanted to go to the strip club!
나만 스트립쇼 못 봤잖아
기회는 많아, 나 물 먹일
여자들이 길에 널렸다고
You'll have plenty of chances.
There are thousands of women out there,
just waiting to screw me over.
Yeah, all right.
그건 그래
- 오빠
- 얘들아
버몬트는 어땠어?
How was Vermont?
Emily is...
에밀리는 정말 놀라워
...incredible. There are
no words to describe her.
달리 표현할 말이 없네
이번 주말은 마치 꿈같았어
The whole weekend was like a dream.
- 그리고 레이첼
- 왔네?
And you! Rach!
You were so right.
- 네 말이 맞았어
- 뭐가?
What?
우린 이제 서로의 행복을
빌어줘야 한다는 얘기...
What you said about us
finally being in a place...
...where we could really
be happy for each other.
I admit, I wasn't quite there.
솔직히 난 그럴 수가 없었어
The thought of you
and that Josh guy
너와 그 조쉬라는 친구...
Joshua.
- 조슈아
Joshua guy at that club,
dancing, having a good time.
네가 그 친구와 클럽에서 즐거운
시간을 보낼 거라고 생각하니까...
And the thought of it kind of....
You know? But now!
알지?
- 그래
- 하지만, 그런데...
But now, I'm totally there.
지금은 그렇지 않아
너처럼 받아들일 수 있어
I'm finally where you are.
오, 정말 다행이다!
Thank goodness!
And thank you for Emily.
덕분에 에밀리를 만났어
천만에, 잘됐다니 다행이네
나도 정말 기뻐
No problem.
I'm so glad I could help, you know?
I'm happy for you.
Happy for you.
너도 잘돼야지
아니, 너나 잘해!
Oh, no, happy for you.
All right. Here's what we'll do.
자, 이렇게 하는 겁니다
You are going to take off
my clothes.
아가씨는 내 옷을 벗겨요
You two, go get the oils.
두 사람은 오일을 가져오고
And you, just constantly scream...
당신은 이렇게 외쳐요
'챈들러는 왕이다! 왕이다! '
..."Chandler's the king!
Chandler's the king!"
I want to be with her.
I like her.
- 난 이 여자 옆에 있을래
- 좋아, 본능에 충실하도록
That's fine.
Go with your instincts!
What am I doing again?
난 뭘 한다고?
제발 한눈팔지 마
이러다 꿈 깬다니까
Pay attention.
I could wake up at any moment.
I'm Joshua.
I'm here to pick up Rachel.
난 조슈아요
레이첼을 데리러 왔소
That's not Joshua.
저 사람 조슈아 아냐
처음 보는데 대충 넘어가
What do you want from me?
I never met the guy.
I'm sorry you can't stay.
아쉽지만 레이첼은 퇴장하고
나머지는 최선을 다해봅시다
The rest of us
have a lot of work to do.
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거죠?
All right, listen.
I got to wake up.
누가 나 좀 깨워줘